Lish mss., 1951-2017 LMC 2404
Lilly Library
- II. Writings
  - By Other Authors
    - Kamine - Kennedy (Box 58)
      - Kaplan, James (Box 58)
        - We Are Fish (Box 58)
      - Karpinski, Michael J. (Box 58)
        - Drive to the Sun (Box 58)
        - Means of Escape (Box 58)
        - My Name is Michael Karpinski [aka These Things That Kill Us] (Box 58)
        - A Place [aka Encounter] (Box 58)
      - Katt, Christian (Box 58)
        - Gordon Lish: Poetics of Fiction (Box 58)
      - Kauffman, Janet, (8 folders) (Box 58)
        - Stories (Box 58)
          - Breaking the News to Doll (Box 58)
          - Coincidence (Box 58)
          - Colleen (Box 58)
          - [Crystal's mother had drunk three beers…] (Box 58)
          - Doing Time (Box 58)
          - Gossip (Box 58)
          - [Her life held a powerful sweetness…] (Box 58)
          - [Lester Koselka, you're a bastard…] (Box 58)
          - [My sister dug her own grave…] (Box 58)
          - Protectorate (Box 58)
          - Round Lake (Box 58)
          - These Three Years (Box 58)
          - When I Walk (Box 58)
        - Collaborators Part 1 (Box 58)
        - Collaborators Full Draft (Box 58)
        - Collaborators Printer's ms. (Box 58)
        - Collaborators Proofs (Box 58)
        - Obscene Gestures for Women Printer's ms. (Box 58)
        - Obscene Gestures for Women Master Galleys (Box 58)
        - Places in the World a Woman Could Walk (Box 58)
      - Keeble, John (Box 58)
        - Saint James at Chief Joseph's Grave or The Transmission (Box 58)
      - Kehoe, John (Box 58)
        - Ths Is Why Hemingway Killed Himself (Box 58)
        - What I'm Looking For [aka I'm Looking for a Job] (Box 58)
      - Kelleher, Hugh (Box 58)
        - Drink the Local Drink (Box 58)
        - My Guys (Box 58)
        - The Story of My Life (Box 58)
      - Kennebeck, Paul (Box 58)
        - End of Service (Box 58)
        - The Exhileration of the Catch (Box 58)
      - Kennedy, Raymond (Box 58)
        - Stories (Box 58)
          - Room Temperature (Box 58)
          - Upstairs, in Our House, Sleeping (Box 58)
        - The Flower of the Republic Draft 1 (Box 58)
        - The Flower of the Republic Draft 2 (Box 58)
        - A Private Station Draft 1 (Box 58)
        - A Private Station Draft 2 (Box 58)
        - A Private Station Draft 3 (Box 58)
        - A Private Station Draft 4 (Box 58)
        - A Private Station Draft 5 (Box 58)
    - Kentfield - Kohler (Box 59)
      - Kentfield, Calvin (Box 59)
        - Who Has Seen the Wind? (Box 59)
      - Kesey, Ken, (3 folders) (Box 59)
        - Writings (Box 59)
          - How Bawble Made Them All Happy (Box 59)
          - Killer (Box 59)
          - Sometimes a Great Notion (Box 59)
          - Untitled Fragment (Box 59)
        - Among the Cows [aka Abdul the Bull and The Varmint in the Dark of the Circle] (Box 59)
        - The Further Inquiry (Box 59)
      - Kestin, Hershel (Box 59)
        - The Man Who Kissed Stalin's Wife (Box 59)
      - Kimball, George Robert (Box 59)
        - The Hat-Check Girl (Box 59)
        - The Tennis King (Box 59)
      - Kimball, Michael (Box 59)
        - Poems (Box 59)
          - After Elizabeth (Box 59)
          - Broken Sex (Box 59)
          - Critical Biography (Box 59)
          - Favors (Box 59)
          - Immortality (Box 59)
          - To Maurice Eidelsberg (Box 59)
          - Mirrors (Box 59)
          - Passage (Box 59)
          - Places I've Been (Box 59)
          - Potty Training (Box 59)
          - To the Editor (Box 59)
          - What Remains of the Day (Box 59)
          - White (Box 59)
        - The Way Our Family Got Away, (3 folders) (Box 59)
        - The Way Our Family Got Away Draft 2 (Box 59)
      - Kirchdorfer, Ulf (Box 59)
        - The Ducks [aka The Pond] (Box 59)
      - Kirkpatrick (Box 59)
        - [From Emily Dickinson's journal] (Box 59)
      - Kirkpatrick, Bear (Box 59)
        - Lemon (Box 59)
      - Kirn, Walter (Box 59)
        - Miles [aka Frequent Flier] (Box 59)
        - The Orphan [aka Life Support] (Box 59)
        - Paying My Calls (Box 59)
        - The Personality of Writing (Box 59)
        - Planetarium (Box 59)
        - Southbound (Box 59)
        - The Steward [aka Plumber's Helper] (Box 59)
        - Used Animals (Box 59)
        - Whole Other Bodies (Box 59)
      - Kitteredge, William (Box 59)
        - In Nevada (Box 59)
        - Pretty Soon There's Nothing There [aka Moon of the Black Calf] (Box 59)
      - Kleinschmidt, Edward (Box 59)
        - Culture Shock (Box 59)
        - Mean (Box 59)
        - Poetry À Go Go (Box 59)
        - Rustique (Box 59)
        - Surplus (Box 59)
      - Kofman, Gil (Box 59)
        - Bashful Bill (Box 59)
      - Kohler, Sheila, (4 folders) (Box 59)
        - Stories (Box 59)
          - Correspondence (Box 59)
          - [It was because of the hat…] (Box 59)
          - [Let me show you where he killed my sister…] (Box 59)
          - Light (Box 59)
          - My Boy's Girl (Box 59)
          - Sisters (Box 59)
          - Trust (Box 59)
        - The House on R Street (Box 59)
        - Secondary Characters (Box 59)
        - Secondary Characters Revisions (Box 59)
      - Konrad, Evelyn (Box 59)
        - The Apparition (Box 59)
        - The Jon (Box 59)
        - O Absalom! (Box 59)
      - Koperwas, Sam (Box 59)
        - Ball [aka A Father's Son] (Box 59)
        - Winner in All Things [aka Slides] (Box 59)
      - Korshak, Sharon (Box 59)
        - Sharon Korshak to Q (Box 59)
    - Koster - Lem (Box 60)
      - Koster, R. M. (Box 60)
        - The Reign of Kiki the First (Box 60)
      - Kotzwinkle, William (Box 60)
        - The Field (Box 60)
        - How Bawble Made Them All Happy (Box 60)
      - Kozlowski, Lynn (Box 60)
        - Being Met (Box 60)
        - Jerry [aka Bad Pets] (Box 60)
        - Scrub (Box 60)
      - Kranes, David (Box 60)
        - Dealer (Box 60)
        - Self Abuse (Box 60)
        - Street (Box 60)
      - Krawiec, Richard (Box 60)
        - Listening to the Gay Boys (Box 60)
        - Lovers (Box 60)
      - Krekorian, Michael (Box 60)
        - Oh, Rauschenberg! (Box 60)
      - Kriesberg, Hadea (Box 60)
        - Siamese (Box 60)
      - Krisak, Len (Box 60)
        - Technical Information (Box 60)
      - Krist, Gary (Box 60)
        - Bone by Bone (Box 60)
      - Krotzer, Minter (Box 60)
        - Making Old-Fashioneds (Box 60)
      - Kubarycz, Brian (Box 60)
        - Chip (Box 60)
        - Hot nor Cold (Box 60)
        - The Instruments I Used (Box 60)
        - On the Mountain (Box 60)
      - Kundera, Milan (Box 60)
        - The Golden Apple of Eternal Desire (Box 60)
        - The Hitchhiking Game (Box 60)
        - Let the Old Dead Make Room for the Young Dead (Box 60)
        - Introduction by Philip Roth (Box 60)
      - Kurtzahn, Leslie (Box 60)
        - Another Dreary Little Poem (Box 60)
      - Kwitny, W. Wood (Box 60)
        - What They Recalled in One Version (Box 60)
      - Lane, Simon (Box 60)
        - Fear (Box 60)
        - The Formalist (Box 60)
        - Twininity, (2 folders) (Box 60)
      - Langer, Suzanne (Box 60)
        - The Great Shift: Instinct to Intuition (Box 60)
      - Larsen, Deborah (Box 60)
        - Deboarh Larsen to Q [aka Dance Notes for the Dogs] (Box 60)
      - Larsen, Eric (Box 60)
        - Spectre: A Writer's Notes (Box 60)
      - Laughlin, James (Box 60)
        - Ez As Waz (Box 60)
        - Harvard, Fair Harvard (Box 60)
        - The Pleasures of Reading the Classics in Translation (Box 60)
      - Leader, Mary (Box 60)
        - Among Things Held at Arms Length (Box 60)
        - A Coastal Story (Box 60)
        - Middle Daughter's Song (Box 60)
        - Trimmed with Eyelet Lace (Box 60)
      - Lear, Patricia (Box 60)
        - After Memphis (Box 60)
        - Believe Me, Phoebe (Box 60)
        - Summer Party (Box 60)
        - Ironman (Box 60)
      - Leaton, Anne (Box 60)
        - Gita's Story (Box 60)
      - Leavitt, David (Box 60)
        - Daguhs and Oonicaws (Box 60)
        - The Dungeon (Box 60)
        - Flight Attendant (Box 60)
        - Fun (Box 60)
        - My Father's Fish (Box 60)
        - In the Radiation Therapy Center (Box 60)
        - The Reindeer (Box 60)
        - White horse Traveler (Box 60)
        - A Woman and Her Dog (Box 60)
      - Lee, Carol (Box 60)
        - Absentmindedly (Box 60)
        - According to Aunt Rose (Box 60)
        - After Getting Rid of Ben (Box 60)
        - Bud (Box 60)
        - Capote's Strange Nostalgia (Box 60)
        - Dining Experience (Box 60)
        - A Evening in Review (Box 60)
        - Fred (Box 60)
        - Hal (Box 60)
        - Helen and Ben (Box 60)
        - In Heaven (Box 60)
        - James, the Photographer (Box 60)
        - Last Night (Box 60)
        - Literary Concerns and the Lives of Poets (Box 60)
        - My Diary (Box 60)
        - Myrna Telling It (Box 60)
        - The Neighbors Observed (Box 60)
        - News (Box 60)
        - Nina (Box 60)
        - One Day (Box 60)
        - Reading About Rita (Box 60)
        - The Remaining Uncle (Box 60)
        - Taylor Street (Box 60)
        - The Thing Is (Box 60)
        - The Way Father Ate an Apple (Box 60)
        - When I Smoked (Box 60)
        - When Ricky Came Home to Lucy (Box 60)
      - Lee, David (Box 60)
        - Snow (Box 60)
        - Sparta Rodeo (Box 60)
      - Leebron, Fred G. (Box 60)
        - Counting (Box 60)
        - Crush (Box 60)
        - Salt Lake City (Box 60)
      - Lefer, Diane (Box 60)
        - Jordan (Box 60)
      - Lelchuck, Alan (Box 60)
        - The Struggless of a Reasonable Man [aka The Confessions of a Reasonable Man] (Box 60)
      - Lem, Stanislaw (Box 60)
        - From the Star Diary: Three Voyages Draft 1 (Box 60)
        - From the Star Diary: Three Voyages Draft 2 (Box 60)
        - From the Star Diary: Three Voyages Draft 3 (Box 60)
    - Lemann (Box 61)
      - Lemann, Nancy (Box 61)
        - Stories (Box 61)
          - Havanna (Box 61)
          - Nancy Lemann to Q (Box 61)
          - [There is a place across Lake Pontchartrain...] (Box 61)
        - How My Heart Broke into a Million Pieces on the Floor, (2 folders) (Box 61)
        - Lives of the Saints Draft, (2 folders) (Box 61)
        - Lives of the Saints Master Pages (Box 61)
        - Lives of the Saints Master Pages - Second Copy (Box 61)
        - Lives of the Saints Author's Masters (Box 61)
        - Lives of the Saints Second Masters (Box 61)
        - Ritz of the Bayou Draft, (2 folders) (Box 61)
        - Ritz of the Bayou Draft 2, (2 folders) (Box 61)
        - Ritz of the Bayou Draft 3, (2 folders) (Box 61)
        - Ritz of the Bayou Draft of Opening (Box 61)
        - Ritz of the Bayou Master Set - First Pass (Box 61)
    - Lemann (end) - Lipsyte (Box 62)
      - Lemann, Nancy (end) (Box 62)
        - Ritz of the Bayou Master Set - Second Pass (Box 62)
        - Ritz of the Bayou Pages (Box 62)
        - Ritz of the Bayou 2 Preprint Manuscripts (Box 62)
        - Copy about Lemann (Box 62)
      - Lemperly, Robert (Box 62)
        - Ass Bandit (Box 62)
        - Gay Ray's Metaphysical Journey (Box 62)
        - Hey, Fairchild [aka Sixteen ] (Box 62)
        - How Bawble Made Them All Happy (Box 62)
        - Pilgrim (Box 62)
      - Lentricchia, Frank (Box 62)
        - Edge of Night, (2 folders) (Box 62)
        - Johnny Critelli Draft 1 (Box 62)
        - Johnny Critelli Draft 2 (Box 62)
        - The Knifemen, (2 folders) (Box 62)
        - Lucchesi and the Whale (Box 62)
        - The Music of the Inferno, (2 folders) (Box 62)
      - Leone, Dan [aka Dom Leone] (Box 62)
        - Ambulanceman (Box 62)
        - Autograph Hound (Box 62)
        - Chemicals [aka Happiness and Nine] (Box 62)
        - I Don Not Have a Dog (Box 62)
        - Job [aka Show Me] (Box 62)
        - Laundryman (Box 62)
        - The Magic Bike (Box 62)
        - Memory Guy [aka If I Had It in Me] (Box 62)
        - Mother [aka Something to Cry About and Minor League Pain] (Box 62)
        - Outside (Box 62)
        - Party [aka Tommy's Party] (Box 62)
        - Responsibleman (Box 62)
        - Soberman (Box 62)
        - The Stapler (Box 62)
        - Tan Sofa with Day Bed (Box 62)
        - Teacherman {aka Door to Door] (Box 62)
        - Team [aka Your Team Is a Losing Team] (Box 62)
        - Wife [aka Do You Know Where Your Alice Is?] (Box 62)
      - Levy-Hinte, Jean (Box 62)
        - Tumors (Box 62)
      - Lesser, Ellen (Box 62)
        - [I started noticing him now and then…] (Box 62)
      - Levine, Matthew (Box 62)
        - Noises of Astonishing Satisfaction (Box 62)
        - When I Go for Her (Box 62)
      - Ligon, Samuel W. (Box 62)
        - Blueboy (Box 62)
      - L'Heureux, John (Box 62)
        - Consolations of Philosophy (Box 62)
      - Lillywhite, Harvey (Box 62)
        - Believing (Box 62)
          - Believing (Box 62)
          - What Can Still Be Told (Box 62)
          - Letter to a Friend (Box 62)
          - Leaving the Light (Box 62)
          - Photographs (Box 62)
          - The Desire to Sail (Box 62)
          - Memorial Day (Box 62)
          - Recovery (Box 62)
          - The Gypsy King (Box 62)
          - Night (Box 62)
          - The Squatter: A Corncrib (Box 62)
          - The Stone Grainary (Box 62)
          - Cherries (Box 62)
          - The Squatter (Box 62)
          - Letting Go (Box 62)
          - For Days We've Been Dreaming (Box 62)
          - Oh Farmers! (Box 62)
          - Tides (Box 62)
          - Ulster Co., New York (Box 62)
          - Napping (Box 62)
          - First Thoughts After Kissing a Woman Who Wears Glasses (Box 62)
          - Waking (Box 62)
          - Makah (Box 62)
          - The Last Note (Box 62)
          - His Bed (Box 62)
          - Ride to Chicago, 1932 (Box 62)
          - Passing Time (Box 62)
          - Returning with My Father (Box 62)
          - Myth (Box 62)
          - To Have Me, Mom Gave Up (Box 62)
          - Walking (Box 62)
          - Above It All (Box 62)
          - The Last Friend (Box 62)
          - Sleep (Box 62)
          - For the Sabbath (Box 62)
          - The Ocean in a Modern Economy (Box 62)
          - Where (Box 62)
          - The Distant Kitchen (Box 62)
          - The Lilac Tree (Box 62)
          - Fire in the Manti LaSalle (Box 62)
      - Lima, Jose Lezama (Box 62)
        - Excerpt from Paradiso (Box 62)
      - Linder, Eric (Box 62)
        - Distress (Box 62)
        - Poem (Box 62)
      - Lipsyte, Sam (Box 62)
        - Kill the Body and the Head Will Die (Box 62)
        - Torquemada (Box 62)
    - Lirenman - Marinovich (Box 63)
      - Lirenman, Ian (Box 63)
        - Judas (Box 63)
      - Lisicky, Paul (Box 63)
        - Tip-It (Box 63)
      - Liu, Timothy (Box 63)
        - The Gates of Hell (Box 63)
        - Say Goodnight (Box 63)
      - Lock, Norman (Box 63)
        - Dreaming Moriarty (Box 63)
        - Explaining Africa (Box 63)
        - Incident in Mombassa (Box 63)
        - The Scream (Box 63)
        - The Sleep Institute (Box 63)
        - Through the Thorns (Box 63)
      - Locklin, Gerald (Box 63)
        - The Criminal Mentality (Box 63)
      - Loomis, Ed (Box 63)
        - Le sujet: un beau livre (Box 63)
          - The Future (Box 63)
          - Tragic Knowledge (Box 63)
          - Manila Bay (Box 63)
          - Tangerines (Box 63)
          - Epigraph (Box 63)
          - Mallarmé (Box 63)
          - The Woman (Box 63)
          - Hello (Box 63)
          - Spiritual Affirmations (Box 63)
          - Poem About the War (Box 63)
          - After Van Gogh (Box 63)
          - Casualty (Box 63)
          - Infantry Duty in Germany (Box 63)
          - A Luftwaffe Base (Box 63)
      - Lowry, John (Box 63)
        - Captains [aka In Dorian's Office] (Box 63)
        - Going Up (Box 63)
        - Out of the Blue (Box 63)
        - Overpopulation (Box 63)
        - Tike (Box 63)
      - Luhn, David (Box 63)
        - The Judith Poems (Box 63)
          - Setting the Tone for Love (Box 63)
          - People, You Say (Box 63)
          - Nostalgie de la Boue (Box 63)
          - Symposium (Box 63)
          - Sojourner: The Superstition Wilderness (Box 63)
          - Clairvoyance (Box 63)
          - A Set of Blinders (Box 63)
          - A Piece Is Where You Find It (Box 63)
          - Passing Visions (for Barbara Siegel) (Box 63)
          - At the Solstice (Box 63)
          - Within Sight of Stony Creek Mountain (Box 63)
          - Do Not for a Moment Mistake This for Aurelius (Box 63)
          - August (Box 63)
          - Triptychs (Box 63)
          - Lacrymosa (for Edward Stierle. 1968-1991) (Box 63)
          - As I Was Saying (Box 63)
          - Drawing by Lots for Voyage (for Talbot Spivak) (Box 63)
          - Against Reverie (Box 63)
          - Attic Likeness (Box 63)
      - Lurie, Morris (Box 63)
        - Captain Fiction Meets the Polish Rapist (Box 63)
        - How to Eat (Box 63)
        - Mud (Box 63)
      - Lutz, Gary, (2 folders) (Box 63)
        - The Assistant (Box 63)
        - Care (Box 63)
        - Carriers (Box 63)
        - Certain Riddances (Box 63)
        - Contractions (Box 63)
        - The Daughter (Box 63)
        - Devotions (Box 63)
        - Education (Box 63)
        - Four (Box 63)
        - Friendship (Box 63)
        - From Where I'm From Now On Hailing From (Box 63)
        - The Gist (Box 63)
        - The Go-Between (Box 63)
        - Halfway (Box 63)
        - Here (Box 63)
        - In on It (Box 63)
        - Left (Box 63)
        - The Man Could Be Heard Doing Things (Box 63)
        - My Bloodbaths (Box 63)
        - Now and Later (Box 63)
        - The Part of the Light I Am No Longer a Part Of (Box 63)
        - The Pavilion (Box 63)
        - Pledge (Box 63)
        - Positions (Box 63)
        - Seeing Supper (Box 63)
        - Slices (Box 63)
        - Susceptibility (Box 63)
        - That Which Is Husbander Than Anything Prior (Box 63)
        - The Time It Takes Me (Box 63)
        - Turns (Box 63)
        - Unnaming the Dog (Box 63)
        - The Versionless Version of My Mother (Box 63)
        - Verson, Recto (Box 63)
        - Vouch for Me [aka Pull and When You Got Back] (Box 63)
        - What They Mean Is What's Behind You (Box 63)
        - Whole (Box 63)
      - Luz, Martin J. (Box 63)
        - Tracing an Epic Graph (Box 63)
      - Lynn, Kirk (Box 63)
        - The Lust Supper (Box 63)
      - Lynch, Thomas (Box 63)
        - Thomas Lynch to Q (Box 63)
        - Skating with Heather Grace Draft (Box 63)
        - Skating with Heather Grace Galleys (Box 63)
        - Skating with Heather Grace Pages (Box 63)
        - Skating with Heather Grace Printer's Proofs (Box 63)
        - Second Tongue (Box 63)
      - Lynds, Dennis (Box 63)
        - Triptych (Box 63)
      - Mace, Paul (Box 63)
        - [Untitled] (Box 63)
      - Maddox, William S. (Box 63)
        - The Christmas Firing Squad (Box 63)
      - Magavern, Sam (Box 63)
        - The Beijing Blind Storytellers Guild (Box 63)
        - Life as a Terrible Gift (Box 63)
        - The Old Black Coat (Box 63)
        - Rabbi Simon's Marriage (Box 63)
        - Winter Time with the Bears (Box 63)
      - Mailer, Norman (Box 63)
        - Of a Small and Modest Malignancy, Wicked and Bristling with Dots (Box 63)
      - Malamud, Bernard (Box 63)
        - The Letter (Box 63)
      - Malick, Terrence (Box 63)
        - Deadhead Miles (Box 63)
      - Maloley, Scott (Box 63)
        - The Proof (Box 63)
      - Malone, Michael (Box 63)
        - Blue Cadillac (Box 63)
        - Synopsis of Dingley Falls (Box 63)
        - The Dingleys of Dingley Falls (Box 63)
      - Malone, Michael (?) (Box 63)
        - How Many Dogs Did Alexander Pope Have? (Box 63)
      - Malzburg, Barry (Box 63)
        - Yearbook (Box 63)
      - Mandell, Arnold (Box 63)
        - Transcendence Training - From the Energy of the First to the Second Second Wind (Box 63)
      - Mano, D. Keith (Box 63)
        - The Call (Box 63)
        - The Death and Life of Harry Goth (Box 63)
      - Marcus, Ben (Box 63)
        - Stories (Box 63)
          - The Animal Husband (Box 63)
          - Continuous Winter, in Law (Box 63)
          - Coughing, in Human Beings, Device (Box 63)
          - Elevation of the Prison Bed (Box 63)
          - False Water Society (Box 63)
          - Intercourse with Resuscitated Wife (Box 63)
          - Landing on Floating Island of the Gods (Box 63)
          - An Open Area Free of Beasts (Box 63)
          - Outline of a City (Box 63)
          - Presentation of the Church (Box 63)
          - Speaking without Breathing (Box 63)
          - Swimming, Strictly, an Inscription (Box 63)
        - The Age of Wire and String Early Drafts (Box 63)
        - The Age of Wire and String (Box 63)
        - Autobiography (Box 63)
      - Marcus, J.S. (Box 63)
        - By J.S. Marcus (Box 63)
        - [When he's in London…] (Box 63)
      - Marcus, Peter (Box 63)
        - The Affair (Box 63)
        - Chesterfield Solitude (Box 63)
        - Minnows (Box 63)
        - This Evening at My Desk a Dark Square Encloses My Mind (Box 63)
      - Marinis, Rick de (Box 63)
        - A Game Without Children (Box 63)
      - Marinovich, Matt (Box 63)
        - Archery at Home and Other Predictions (Box 63)
        - Flash On [aka Making the Circuit] (Box 63)
        - Food (Box 63)
        - Help Me! [aka Serum] (Box 63)
        - Intelligence (Box 63)
        - A Little Vivaldi (Box 63)
        - Making Headway [aka Small Victories] (Box 63)
        - Our Latest Accomplishments (Box 63)
        - Spoken For (Box 63)
        - You Can't Leave Me Here (Box 63)
    - Markus - Meats (Box 64)
      - Markus, Peter (Box 64)
        - Openings (Box 64)
      - Marowitz (Box 64)
        - Fantasizing Lisskulla (Box 64)
      - Márquez, Gabriel García, (2 folders) (Box 64)
        - The Incredible and S ad Tale of Innocent Erendira and Her Heartless Grandmother, (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - Marten, Eugene (Box 64)
        - The Apologist (Box 64)
        - 'Doesn't Anybody Here Speak English?' (Box 64)
        - Goat's Eye (Box 64)
        - He Said the Bombing Had Started (Box 64)
        - Liquids Continue to Conspire (Box 64)
        - Vista (Box 64)
      - Martinez, Manuel (Box 64)
        - Melaleuca (Box 64)
      - Martone, Michael (Box 64)
        - Alive and Dead in Indiana Printer's ms. (Box 64)
        - Alive and Dead in Indiana Galleys, (2 folders) (Box 64)
        - Alive and Dead in Indiana Master Galleys (Box 64)
        - Alive and Dead in Indiana Pages, (2 folders) (Box 64)
        - Alive and Dead in Indiana Proof (Box 64)
        - Untitled Collection of Stories (Box 64)
          - March of Dimes (Box 64)
          - Nein (Box 64)
          - Lost (Box 64)
          - X-Ray (Box 64)
          - The Third Day of Trials (Box 64)
          - An Accident (Box 64)
          - Vocation (Box 64)
      - Marvel, Mark (Box 64)
        - [It is the night that they come…] (Box 64)
        - [The pig corn field is where…] (Box 64)
      - Matanle, Stephen (Box 64)
        - Burning Windows (Box 64)
        - Commissioned by a Wealthy Uncle to Write a Poem for His Birthday, I Remind Myself of Holbein's Portrait [aka Reading the Personal Ads I Think of Holbein's Portrait (Box 64)
        - His Insomnia (Box 64)
      - Materath, Mario (?) (Box 64)
        - Literary Creative and the Publishing Industry: A Round Table (Box 64)
      - Matthews, Jim (Box 64)
        - The Ballad of Rube and Silky (Box 64)
      - McCall, Bruce (Box 64)
        - At the 1936 Cairo World's Fair (Box 64)
      - McCloud, Kate (Box 64)
        - [I finished Mojave late last night…] (Box 64)
      - McDonald, Craig Anton (Box 64)
        - The War at Home (Box 64)